This could be the start of a majestic romance
A Royal Queens Christmas is a tv movie, comedy,
romance film directed by Lee Friedlander.
A prince finds his way to Queens during Christmas when a local woman
enlists his help with a children's Christmas show.
Dee Dee, played by Megan Park.
Colin, played by Julian Morris.
Whitbey, played by Michael Hanrahan.
Zoe, played by Nicola Correia Damude.
Mickey, played by Tony Nappo.
Angie Paretti, played by Ramona Milano.
The King's Christmas message (or The Queen's Christmas message in a queen's reign), formally as His Majesty's Most Gracious Speech, and informally as the Royal Christmas
message is a broadcast made by the sovereign of the United Kingdom and the other Commonwealth realms to the Commonwealth of Nations each year at Christmas.
The tradition began in 1932 with a radio broadcast by King George V via
the British Broadcasting Corporation's Empire Service.
The message is broadcast on television, radio, and
the Internet via various providers.
It is usually broadcast at 15:00 GMT on Christmas Day.
Unlike some other speeches, such as the King's Speech at the State Opening of Parliament which is written by the government,
the Christmas speech is a personal message written by the monarch with input from spouses and direct advisors.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, prince, royalty, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.